= 2.0.1.64 =
- fixed bug when Log panel hiding if you're starting new list after error;
- trying to fix issue with "freezing" downloading;
- fixed IOHandler error when log on derpiboo.ru;

= 2.0.1.63 =
- now you can set your own Max. Threads Count and Delay between queries and pictures for every resource. Check a resource's special settings from the New List or the Settings screen. You can't get more max. threads than defined in the resource's script or in Download settings, also you can't set less delay than defined in the script as well;
- fixed a resource settings saving from Settings sreen;
- a saving path and a display label now changes for an album's pictures in the pixiv;
- now you can download user's scraps from the furrafinity;
- added the thedoujin.com. You need to input doujin's ID instead of Tag;

= 2.0.1.62 =
- fixed a bug  that causes trouble with downloading non "_big" pictures from albums in the pixiv;
- fixed getting albums from the pixiv (manga mode template is changed);
- fixed an album's pictures naming (.jpg_123456789 bug) in the pixiv;

= 2.0.1.60 =
- fixed a "picture not assigned" bug for the pixiv when downloading albums;
- fixed download "pausing" without finishing (nothing downloading, but not all pictures finished) when downloading albums;
- now titles will update in pixiv with enabled "Get tags" option, without that option titles is shortened to 24 symbols;
- now albums uses album's first picture directory for a "saving path" field;
- fixed selection using "Check *" option for albums (not working inside albums);

= other =

- Not that soon how I wanted, but now you can download pools from gelbooru. Pools looks like 1 page with all pictures in it (like 1.5k pics on 1 page), and because of it gathering can be slower;
- fixed page counting for donmai.us;

= 2.0.1.59 =

- added danbooru2 template;
- donmai.us now working on danbooru2 template;
- added feature to make cycles in scripts;
- danbooru2 template allows to download pools (searching by part of name or ID);
- you can now download pools from donmai.us;
- old danbooru template now allows to download pools too, but searching only by ID;
- now you can download pools from behoimi.org, e621.net, konachan.com, twentypercentcooler.net, yande.re. Maybe from wildcritters too, but they're not working now and I can't check it. Sankaku trying their best in blocking access as always;

= 2.0.1.58 =

- reworked xml parsing. Now parser normally handle all common errors in html;
- sankaku is fixed (because of new parsing);
- not all pictures finding on deviantart is fixed (because of new parsing);
- getting tags on lolibooru is fixed (trimming newline symbols);
- mgbooru.net added;

= 2.0.1.57 =

- thanks to resource owners, who never support common rules of naming for tags and other stuff (do not use isolator symbol in isolated string, like 'str'ing'; do not use " />" if tag have content inside; ), xml-parser have been "enchanted" to avoid stupid popular errors of imposers. Now parser have more harder rules, and most of scripts is slightly changed. I'm sure there will be bugs;
- fixed downlaod from pixiv;
- added 2 new options for the "by userid" mode: "works (userid in tags)" and "favorites (userid in tags)". How description says, if option choosen, userid will be taken from tag-string. This options needed to use "create tag list" feature for the list of authors from pixiv;
- added mgbooru.net;
- added "Use distribution by resources" option in settings. There you're can disable distribution of threads between all of them (all downloads will work by the list);
- added the searching tag on the "Common"->"General" tab of the downloading page;
- enjoy new circle of the testing hell!
- fixed furrafinity.net;

= 2.0.1.56 =

- added feature to create keyword lists. You can input list of keywords to start downloading from the same resource using different tags ("..." button near tag string -> Create tag list);
- fixed downloading from deviantart.com (added token verification for direct download urls, now getting of direct url is slower);
- sankaku changed template AGAIN. This time they replaced pages with '<<' '>>' buttons, BUT they used '<>' symbols instead of &lt; &gt; codes (at the same time using &amp; code for '&', thanks to the engine, apparently). If "smart" browsers can handle this blunder, but common xml-parsers can't. Now I must "fix" this stupidness. Where is my web 1.0 and netscape...

= 2.0.1.55 =

- fixed weird "Could not convert variant of type (OleStr) into type (Double)" error on the "New list" page;

= 2.0.1.54 =

- fixed bugs in getting vartime dates (for "d","m","h" and "am" keys);
- added e-shuushuu.net;

= 2.0.1.53 =

- now chan/idol.sankakucomplex uses queue to prevent "too many" error. By tests, it must by ~2500ms. I hope they do not return back that DDoS protection thing;
- fixed little bugs when threads sometime skips their queue;
- changed "what's new" window style;

= 2.0.1.52 =

- fixed that devart downloaded only featured pictures;
- fixed pages counting when getting list;
- fixed the last used name format saving;
- fixed AV when trying to change name format from settings screen using format editor;
- fixed bug when pictures do not marked as "skipped";
- added feature to add delay between queries for the "not fast downloding allowed" resources (like sankaku);
- and just after I added that delay option, sankaku added the "Browser Verification", what means I need to simulate browser window to pass it. In another words, I think I'll give up on supporting sankaku, too many brainfuck;
- now you can download Mature and Adult pictures from furaffinity.net, but it works only if you're logged in, and "18+" option is activated in your profile;

= other =

- applyed changes in derpiboo.ru engine;
- now you can download spoilered pictures from derpibooru;


= 2.0.1.51 =

- now on the "New list" page, if the remembered list exists, Step 2 will be set automatically;
- fixed mnemonica translating from HEX codes;
- now if in list resource added more then once, they're share their thread pool. It means if maximum thread count per resource is 2, then all the same resources will have maximum 2 threads at the same time in sum;
- added queued list getting for resources, where used POST-requests to initiate process. It means next resource will not start getting list while previous resource not finished;


= other =

- added analbooru.com;
- fixed downloading of new formated "img-inf" urls from an albums and an author's pages. Because of this changes downloading will be much slower;
- nekobooru.net changed to neko.booru.org. Actually, for me it's totally retarded resource right now. Maybe it's temporary;

= 2.0.1.50 =

- fixed a bug with downloading and displaying the pixiv album pictures;
- fixed downloding a "img-inf" urls bug from pixiv;

= 2.0.1.49 =

- fiexd a bug when tags don't get a tagstring to search (resources starts to search everything or nothing);
- fixed a bug (I hope) with apostrophes in tagstring;
- there is one more hard to catch bug with downloading from MANY resource at the same time. People, why did you realy download from all 20 + resources at the same time?

= 2.0.1.48 =

- added feature to add the same resource more than once;
- now grabber automatically get protocol for the "relative protocol" urls. From the referer or "http" as default. Also now grabber will try to get full url for a relative urls from the referer;
- now the path editor displays only fields that available for current resource (or all if global);

= other =

- fixed an url making error on the furaffinity (can't identify protocol);
- fixed another url making error on the furaffinity with an unicode symbols in it;
- fixed paging on the pixiv when getting list from the user's works and favorites;
- fixed getting "author" field from the user's works in the pixiv;
- added alternative way to get page count in classic danbooru template (fix for sankaku);

= 2.0.1.47 =

- added feature to delete already downloaded duplicates by it's MD5-sum (Advanced > Delete duplicates by MD5, check new button in main menu); 
- fixed deviantart getting list error when loading from the user's gallery;
- fixed getting title for pics from the user's gallery;

= 2.0.1.46 =

- fixed a little bug with big mathematical expressions calculation in a scripts;
- added comicartcommunity.com;

= 2.0.1.45 =

- added anime-pictures.net;
- now, after picture downloaded, full path to it will be updated;

= 2.0.1.44 =

- fixed donmai.us work, using old API. Because of mechanics of the New Danbooru Engenie now grabber can't download many pages at the same time;

= 2.0.1.42 =

- fixed a bug of replacing ":" when using urls in the name format (using %post_url%);

= 2.0.1.39 =

- now, when file name is creating, in a %key% does no changing the "\" symbol to the safe "_" symbol;

= 2.0.1.38 =

- fixed some bugs with $fn$, not all anyway;
- added titles for the DArt;
- fixed downloading from the DArt if a categories not selected;
- renamed %categorypath% to %category% for the DArt to avoid misunderstandings;

= 2.0.1.37 =
- added deviantart.com. You can download from the search page, the gallery and the user's favorites;
- added feature to enable logging (it means copies of downloaded pages will be saved to the ".\log" directory). In the future i want to add debugging messages that can be declarated in the resource script;
- all another just cosmetics;

= 2.0.1.35 =

- first critical bug in update, I hope not too much people downloaded version 2.0.1.33, otherwise they're need to download updater manualy and reinstall grabber;

= 2.0.1.33 =

- fixed max 50kb download speed for a speed limit feature;
- fixed a bug of an encoding identification, because of which some special symbols is broken in a tags (now Grabber think  it's always  UTF-8, hope it will be);
- favorite tags, saving paths and etc now saving in unicode, as must be;
- faxed a "one pic for album" downloading bug (and following infinite errors) if downloading more then one album at the same time;
- added indication for albums downloading;
- in the pixiv for pics in albums removed fields "id" and "title", use "album_id" and "album" instead;
- the pixiv follows the trend and one more time changed layout, searching is fixed, and "empty" promo pictures as well;

= other =

- updated a script for derpiboo. Link format for pic is changed, and because of it url becomes incorrect (why they're leaving '://' without 'http' now?)
- fixed error on danbooru-boards;

= 2.0.1.xx =

= 2.0.1.30 =

- fixed a bug that preventes realisation of loading from danbooru GUI;
- fixed a bug when you need to check a settings of minitokyo at least once to download from it;
- fixed sankaku work;

= 2.0.1.27 =

- fixed a few more bugs that cause a criticals;
- tips now can be disabled in settings;
- for pixiv added user-works and user-favorites modes. Set a check near "Use user id", input an user id and select source (works or favorites);

= 2.0.1.26 =

- ALOT more stable now. If you see more bugs - let me know, I try fix it as possible.

= 2.0.1.24 =

/ huge update with a bunch of changes that can cause a new bugs. I'll try to list "visible" changes, what I remember:
- now you can limit the download speed (Settings -> Threads -> Speed);
- list of supported resources is growing, and searching of needed become harder. Added the field allows you to filter the list.
- now you can save your favorite queries (buttons with stars next to the tags field in the "new list" mode);
- at the request of inattentive people, suffering about small and unnoticeable buttons, added a hint showing where to click to start a pics downloading;
- released mechanism of album storing;
- added the postprocessing mode (editional pics processing after list is finished);
- added pixiv.net. There is "Get tags" mode for a pics. In this mode, after list is finished, postprocessing get tags and r-18 rating for a pics.

= other =

- other changes too old. Too lazy to translate;